From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake and don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Okay, yeah, hey, look, I'm here. Oh look, I'm here. Hold on. No, look, come on
You sitting behind me. He's behind me. Wrong song fix. Oh look, I'm here. Hi, what's wrong?
Little baby
I think so thank you so much for letting me know. It's kind of hard to see my screen. Hi guys
It's all uh, honestly on it
Word maybe go hey guys, so
Oh, it's hot today here
So I did I only got one uh one guy looking for like the what the uh
Scrap metal today, but he knocked on the door. He's like hi
I was like I said hello like what are you looking for? He's like
Well, I'm here for the scrap metal and I was like, oh
I don't have any scrap metal. There's just anything what he's like. No, I just talked to you on the phone
I like no that wasn't me
that was like
Some some uh, he's like what and I was like, it's just some good
It's uh, I think called the guy he's like as they call the guy and say that um, you know, he's just some
Con artist and you know go fuck himself, and he's like oh my god
He was like so mad. I don't even get that Matt. I mean, I wasn't really
I mean, I don't get mad really it's like what I'm they take it to say hi to somebody but yeah
He got really bad this guy. Oh, it was sad
It's like it really is like
Worse on these people like because they have to like drive like all the way down and it's really hard to turn the car
Oh my god, it's just like a pain in the butt. I guess he's ruining like all these other people say it doesn't really like bother me at all
It's like
They're not it's not like they like
Well one time he said he was gonna have them like take off my metal door and stuff like that and take it for scum
It'll put no one's gonna do that and if they did I would you know, but hey, what's that for?
Oh, I mean, that's just like a little bit too, but hey, Root. Hey, over here. Oh, baby. Oh, baby
Yeah, gangstalk. It is gangstalking and I was watching something today about gangstalking. It was like oh
Look, I mean, it was like kind of professionally made but it was like oh look how stupid these people are
They're just like there. You know, there's paranoid
Mentally ill drug addicts and they're so afraid of you know, like they hear a helicopter or something
Yeah, there is cases of people that are paranoid and like but basically I can tell you a little bit how it works
Because I've experienced things like this and then that was okay now I'm gonna get like oh my god is the kids weird
No, here's what happens
It's like a form of like basically narcissistic abuse on steroids where it's like and it is like basically if you have more than one
But there's certainly right because this thing I watched was like basically nobody's ever it never happened in the in the history of the world
No one's ever been stuck. I mean Jesus was gangsta. That's the original person. I was getting stopped right
betrayed by the one circle and
You know eventually like you know torture put on a cross or whatever
But you know slander and so it's a lot of stuff that goes with it
But part of it is like this narcissistic abuse if you study narcissistic abuse like there's a lot of tactics like one of them is
One of them is trigger you see set so they set these triggers on you and so this is a really easy thing
Like wait for it to have so imagine like how effective this can be if people are mentally ill in the first place and that's why it's like
really, really insidious, insidious, it can be, right?
Because the people are prone to that
and then you're fucking with them
and they're already prone to that.
They might have even on their own sort of being paranoid.
Now it's like you're giving them reasons to be paranoid.
Okay, that's one thing, but setting triggers.
So for example, someone drives a car and then you like...
put a purple marker on top of the car and then when they get out go outside like okay
That's weird and then they go to work and they come out
They've had a purple marker and there's a purple marker on the car and they're like oh my okay. That's
Is that a coincidence? No, that's impossible. But you know and
Then let's say they didn't go to work and on their desk is a purple marker and then they go home and it's like on there
It's like and then it's like all of a sudden
There doesn't need to be any purple markers any time the person ever encounters a purple marker again in their life
They're probably gonna be like, you know, it's like because it programs and so it's a trigger programs triggers and things like that
I can get go into it. I think I'll do a presentation on some of the pain Lenore. I'll do a presentation on it sometime on
Kind of like the more insidious forms of abuse because I've been through I've been trained by Russia basically
I've been trained by Russian, right?
Celebrities are stocked. It comes with the territory. Well, I'm not really a celebrity
I mean it's like a celebrity to get to have you know security and they get to have like a big mansion gates and stuff like that
You know kind of more scary when it's like somebody without
Really protection and part of the thing about it is isolating people especially from there
Like they're a circle of like loved ones. They get them to suspect everybody and so
That may kind of lose protection. A lot of it's about trying to make the person unalive themselves
Yeah, I'm gonna go into a little bit because I'm Alexander mayor was I posted this or she I posted this on my wall
But she posted this a while ago right before we started doing our triple series, you know, and this was about
You know, this is called you know, somebody hits, you know, I think I forgot
I don't know who who was making the comments because she doesn't really mention who they are who they were but it was like some I
Can guess who it was right? It's not not some woman who a
It's a woman with kids so hold on, but I'll show you hold on
Because she talks about some of like the same things that are happening and said about me
We're set about her and it's like I just like wow
That's pretty crazy. It's like I relate to her so much, but I want you to see a little bit of this
This presentation she did it's called you can't prove how anything smells or
Or what taste with heels or the internet
Share this I mean I'll comment on it along the way
But and I'm not going to play the whole thing, but I'm gonna
Really want you to see some of this though. Oh my gosh, that's scary. That's not it
Some of you okay, hold on to where that was designed specifically to grow when it comes
you know
timeframe that we're in the only two senses our sight and hearing
unless something's visual or audio,
the internet cannot really relay much of anything to you.
There's three senses missing.
Touch, taste, and smell.
And that's very important to keep in mind
when it comes to the tack.
Hey, Natalie.
That certain bullies.
or people who want to pick paint false narratives about others utilized.
When I was first heavily attacked and disappointed in people started coming after me
in a way that was designed specifically to coerce me to suicide many years ago.
I'm talking back in
It was really heavy for me around 2013.
One of the things that they came after me about, and I'm talking about certain nefarious people within the adult entertainment industry.
I'll actually show you one of them because he's currently in prison for a very, very, very long time.
From what I've been told attempted to reach out to him if they did they're now on a federal watch list
Just saying now
But the way that that do came after me
The false narrative and the false rumor that I have that hygiene. I'm actually the opposite
I'm naturally OCD obsessive compulsive disorder
He said that I smelled though. He'd never met me in person. I'd never met that man that I just showed you
Within these communities people picked up the false and narratives that he painted about me and
Then expanded he also was the person I want to show him to you again
curious
He put out the false narrative that unfortunately stuck for many years, that I have HIV or AIDS.
I've never had HIV or AIDS.
And I just want to know, like, that's one of the things being said about me too.
There's actually someone running around, HIV Awakens Tarot.
You know, I see in the chat slot. Oh sidekits HIV AIDS
I mean, I didn't even know HIV was the thing really anymore
I thought that was kind of like out with the 80s, but and I was always very like
STD phobic and so I really am like pretty like
Almost sell a bit like I've almost I'm almost I'm practically a version believe it or not, but okay, so go. Let's hear this
Never was with anyone who had HIV or AIDS, but you see, all the things that he was saying were things that could not be proven at all.
I really don't like the way that I saw Psyche Awakens Tarot attack today on a live stream hosted by a woman.
who definitely doesn't like being attacked unjustly,
but she was willing to do it to him.
I will never speak to that woman again.
And that woman knows exactly who she is.
I know she's talking about it too much.
She actually set a very bad example for her children today.
I hope her children never see that live stream.
I hope they never see what their mother is capable of.
I pray that they never know.
Because it was wrong what she did have anyone in these has anyone in these communities ever met in person psyche I
Bet not I
Bet not you all like to attack him because he has a multitude of cats
Now I don't know psyche well. I've known
For a little while before we but it's just recently that I spoke to him
And I just really felt like I connected with him when I spoke to him
I'm really looking forward to doing this three-part series if he still gives me the chance to do so. Hopefully
He will the first one is scheduled for tomorrow at noon my time zone
but um
I felt that the woman who conducted the panel, as she did today, did so in effort to not
only discredit his professionalism, but to make him really feel bad, maybe to where he
would think to himself, oh, Alex might be friends with this girl.
I don't want Alex to have to pick and choose.
I'm not going to do the three-part series with her.
Was that the agenda?
Or did you get paid to do it?
Or are you just a nasty witch?
That's what people are trying to figure out.
But you don't know what psyche situation is.
None of you do.
I definitely don't know.
Am I in love with him?
No.
I like him.
Why is it with some of you?
To where and I actually you tried to leave me a nasty comment earlier. You're blocked
But why is it that some of you think that being nice?
Or liking someone or treating someone the way that you would want to be treated equates
to
Romantic love
This $60 heated vest was developed for us special forces, but now finally available to the public and it's flying off
Are you all that sheltered really?
Do you never socialize?
Do you not have friends?
What is wrong with some of you?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
But for those of you out there trying to paint
the false narrative,
a narrative that you definitely cannot prove.
Saying, oh, the psyche smells, you don't know that.
You're trying to drive that man nuts.
That's what you're trying to do and you're trying to isolate him because some of you think it's funny to try to control people over the internet. It's not funny.
It's sick. Very sick.
So you said that he smells. You can't prove that. You're saying he doesn't take care of his cats. His cats are obviously very well taken care of.
He probably adopts a lot of cats and a lot of single people tend to do that.
especially when they're over the age of 30.
What I do know is that you guys are making him feel really bad,
and that's sick. And all of you doing it, I am quietly watching,
and I'm quietly figuring out who's doing what.
And those of you doing it, I will never speak to you again.
because those of you okay with hurting him are the same people who are okay with hurting me.
And other people who are like he or I.
I'm noble.
When I came into these communities, a lot of you jumped on a lot of bandwagons because you hate black people.
You're bigots and you're prejudiced and you're racist.
Because he's openly a part of the lgbtq community to my knowledge.
You don't like that and you think you can get away with it all of you attacking him you're actually engaging in hate crime, you know.
You might not be saying certain words, but a lot of you have a certain track record.
And it's being noted.
I remember how bad it made me feel when I would go live as a webcam body.
And I would have not just 10 not just 20, but sometimes upwards to 100 people.
coming in my chat
Saying some of the worst of the worst things to me
Simply because I was calling out some really bad people in the adult industry and again
I want to show you who was behind it because I think it's important for you all to realize the types of people who are behind these types of
Hate campaigns. He looks like your everyday Joe, doesn't he?
Look at his rap sheet
See this guy
This guy was who is behind an
Extreme heat campaign that almost did push me over the edge
Turned out that he was a complete extortionist
Engaged in all kinds of financial fraud
Beat the shit out of his wives and girlfriends
When as far as to not only abuse children, that wasn't enough for him. He abused animals too
Yet you have the parties
Allegedly on rumour petto.com trying to reach out to this dude to find out about me really
good, I
Want you to because you'll find out a lot
but what I'm saying is that it's not okay what you're doing to psyche and
Those of you who engaged in something today, and it's not it's not it's about the principle of it. I
Barely know psyche, but I'll tell you what I really do like people who are very into
Spirituality doesn't matter what spirituality is that they're into if they're into if they're knowledgeable. That's my kind of person
And he really does have a gift.
He's not bullshitting.
He might actually have more than just the gift
of present readings.
He might be able to do some other things
to where he hasn't realized it yet.
My friends are not only people
who only subscribed to Christianity.
Someone who I really like in this community,
the only reason I don't talk to him anymore
is because of who he's dating.
MC Frosty. He's openly Luciferian or Satanist. I still consider him a friend even though I
don't touch base with him. A man dealing with daily foot pain and neuropathy symptoms started
using the Emsen's wearable therapy device. Sorry. And the only reason I don't is because
That is someone who I consider a threat. I know I know a lot of tarot readers. I know a lot of spiritualists
So it rocks. I know a lot of ministers and I know a lot of pastors. See our UEL is that great? That's right
That's my crowd
But what I am here to say in video format so that you all can see I mean what I say
It's that I don't want anyone who engages in that kind of thing around
Sages at all, online or offline anymore.
No more.
It's too hurtful.
I'm enough sage.
Turned me into somebody that I don't like being
Some of you wonder why I stand up for people as I do why I've done certain things that I've done is because of that man that I showed you
Like I said he wanted to kill me
He didn't and the reason that he didn't was because I decided I wanted to live
Some of you don't want me to be like he's friend. I want very much to be his friend
Maybe more so than he wants to be my friend
And I want to be his friend because I want to see him live and I want to see him flourish
And be successful. He's built something good for himself
And a lot of you are very jealous correct Natalie
He is gifted my traveling tarot, I'm just now looking at the chat
I'm just now looking.
I want to highlight with my gypsy tarot stud.
There it is.
My traveling gypsy tarot. Yes.
He is, he's very gifted, extremely so.
To the women around you where we're little house on the prairie looking dresses and the men wear suits all the time
Are you carpenters, maybe?
He has a lot of soul in his eyes a lot
So that's all I'm saying
And I don't I don't smell good. I probably smell like, um, she smells good cigarettes and
Keep body spray at the moment. That's probably what I smell like
A lot of you wouldn't like what I smell like so leave me alone, but leave him and his cats alone, please
Leave them alone
He loves those cats those cats probably wouldn't have anywhere to go if he wasn't taking care of them and
Who is anyone to dictate really if the cat if the animals are obviously thriving
How they should be taken care of I don't have any pets right now
But I did it once upon a time and I was not always a perfect pet owner hardly anybody is
Hardly anybody
But
Hold on a second when it comes to him in some other people what does person say?
You're not a projected class psyche. You're just a gay in cell. Okay. My call who is you know
What does that he's actually what the man?
Let me see federal hate crime law. Let me just look at it
Let me see
Okay, hate crime acts, let me see.
Offenses involving actual perceived race, color, religion, or national origin.
Okay, so maybe they don't have, oh, hold on, hold on.
But, oh yeah, here it is.
In general, whoever, whether or not acting under color of law in any circumstance described in subparagraph B,
willfully cause bodily injury to any person, or through the use of a firearm or dangerous weapon
or explosive or incendiary device attempts to cause bodily injury to any person
because of actual perceived religion, national origin, gender, sexual orientation,
gender identity or disability of any person, shall be imprisoned not more than 10 years
find in accordance with this title or both, shall be imprisoned for any term of years
or for life, find in accordance with this title or both, if death results from the offense
or the offense includes kidnapping or attempt to kidnap aggravated sexual abuse or an attempt
to commit aggravated sexual abuse or attempt to kill.
Oh yeah, so it does say sexual orientation in there, okay?
Don't know I wouldn't say I'm an incel either because you know, I got a you know, Chris K's you know
interested in you know doing some chatter bait, so
What?
I guess I'm not quite that much of an incel
No, I'm kind of like you know and
Incels stands for involuntary celibate. I could have sex every day if I wanted to I could you know how easy it is for me
To go on to Grindr and meet somebody
It would be very, very, very simple.
If I want, but it is so simple that
it's not that attractive of a thing to me.
Plus, it's like, like I said, I'm like very,
you know, kind of phobic.
I'm looking for love and not like, you know, sex.
But anyway, so anyway, good.
So you're wrong, my call,
and hopefully you're already banned from the chat.
Stop.
Especially if you're not really doing anything so many of you are faceless
You're afraid to come on camp my call
each I'd be a weakens tarot and
Allied a
Lot of you are afraid to even live so I've seen your face
I've given a lot of support to a lot of you I've defended a lot of you
And I've donated to one of you two and I'll regret it
Do you know when it's trying to kidnap you or delete? Oh, really? It's all learning. I didn't I'm not having people
You know, he's threatening that taught me a
lot
About this world when it comes to
How we have a long way to go as humans
Throw away your reading glasses computer glasses, and yes, even your sunglasses. This is the last pair of glasses
You'll ever need
Introducing the revolutionary auto-focus glass
I'll be basically, you know the worst thing to happen, right?
I think
Probably does drive someone else who has a live stream live criticize
But if I've come to an understanding with Krakatana, I think it probably drives Krakatana crazy
that
They will not completely acknowledge
Extraterrestrial and interdimensional life just yet. You want to know why?
Because of how
People like psyche
How so many humans have treated people like me, how it's driven people like me, and when you fight back to such an extent that I've mistakenly attacked some of the wrong people.
It's bad.
Thank you. Thank you, Jamie.
My claw. Bye.
Yeah, people actually creating real content.
And then you have people who are nothing but co-tailwriters
stealing the content to create
what is a poor excuse of content,
just so they can profit off that
and drive the original creator off social media
and then try to claim that they have complete rights
to it and own it.
It's a method of trying to steal somebody's soul.
it's okay he's that's the guy that's talking
i don't like disingenuous compliments from faceless people
someone like my traveling gypsy tarot i can kind of feel who that is
it's allied
because i have a certain gift too
But some of you, you don't feel like anything to me.
You feel empty.
Misery feels empty to me.
It'll be a good stream. It'll be three three p.m. Eastern Standard, okay?
Basically a topic is good. That was actually something that I just learned about
I'm really excited to talk to do the free. I was having memory. Oh my god. I
Think that there's Christine. Oh my I'm just kidding. Okay, but I'm so sorry. So sorry. No, I did not mean
Did not mean that that was a joke that was a joke and now I'm being mean now. I'm being mean
okay
I'm just oh, that was so me. I'm so sorry. I mean
No, come on. I'm the fucking dick my dick
Okay, anyway
I'm a fucking, I know I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I did not mean it, I did not mean it, I'm fucking, I know, okay Jamie, Jamie, I'm sorry, Jamie, by the way, you can go find her, she's around too, I see her every day, are you doing a panel, of course, no, I was just teasing, I'm just teasing, that was a bad joke, it was a terrible joke.
Come on up. Come on up. I know boy. Who's calling boy boy?
Who are you calling boy Mike Jaws? Mike Jaws?
Here you go. Not you know beast. Oh my gosh. Oh don't even don't say things that I think you know
Religion would be under that too. I'm gonna make sure this is my friend Natty. Nat. I don't see you coming at the home
Put this on. Hello. Can you hear me? Yes. Hi, Tweety. Hi, how are you? Yeah, I'm all right. Not too bad.
Good. I don't know if you, yeah. You know, have you seen Alexandra before? Like, I actually, that was before I did.
I've seen her before, but I don't really know the woman very well.
She's really cool. I actually she came out to meet me recently. We went to Hollywood at dinner and stuff and she's just
Delighted just as nice as she is on person as she is on a she's just awesome. I love her
I'm not speaking the one day. Yeah
Yeah, I looked at me like there's a lot of people that are so great and I would love to meet and it's like, you know
I hope I do get a chance. You know, everyone can smell me for themselves, but she didn't smell me
She said it's no fine. She said it's no fine
Maybe a little hot, but it's a little hot. I might not be perfect right now, but I don't naturally have like this disgusting
I don't know. I'm like less the probably less
dirty than some people think because everyone's just head in their mind that it's just like I'm just
Actually, my house is looking really good at laundry going
Backing good right now. So I'm comfortable. How are you doing?
Yeah, I'm alright. Not too bad
I'm swimming in the ocean right now. I love the ocean behind me. I love it
That's Mr. Rudy. This is Rudy. Have you seen Rudy? There's Rudy and I got Tricks behind me too,
Tricks. He's looking over the, he's looking over the banister because yeah, we have people knocking
on the door, you know, and all the times of the day now, so... Well, my dog's sleeping in the
background. I can tell the visual effect, though. Thank you guys for getting, for getting with me,
but I'm gonna have a lot of trolls, you know, there's... Totally, my dog's on the chain.
That big fluffy, that little fluffy thing.
Oh.
He's so cute. I love him.
He can ease her.
She's a black and tan Yorkshire Terrier.
Oh Yorkie. Oh yeah.
And it's like, you know,
well here like around the face with her here
because she doesn't let me,
she'll let me shave anywhere else.
Well, she won't let me get near her face, so she's on the lion's mane.
My mom loves Yorkie.
She's had a couple teacup Yorkies, like the little teeny little dogs.
And one of them has, like, one of them lost its leg.
And so it has, like, you know, but also my sister, like, is also, like, she had,
my sister adopted a dog with missing front leg, you know, like a little dog.
You know, my family loves animals.
My mom is a huge animal lover.
She would always have all kinds of animals
as she keeps growing up.
Well, we've had her for three years.
I wouldn't like tropical fish,
but I don't know how to look after tropical fish.
My dad used to have tropical fish.
Hey, Nancy.
Yeah, I'm so I might have some more a lot of trolls in here today because you know
Disagreements I've had with some certain people. I mean, of course
You probably get my trolls as well. So you're probably get other trolls. Well
So we were together and we were together were stronger we can even like you know, what can I do really it's like, you know
We have supported people, it makes such a difference, you know, when you're really, you know, people are going after you because it's like, just to have somebody to understand.
And I really appreciated, like, you know, Alexander's doing that live.
I remember I had watched them play most of it, but it was really, really sweet.
Women are not responsible for the sins of men. What does that mean, sin men?
The sin of men. Let's see. Well, women are not responsible for the sins of men. Well, they're
saying, I think he's talking about Adam and Eve a little bit. Like, you know, they've always blamed
Eve, or they blame Lilith, or they blame Pandora. It's always like this female curiosity that
you know as I think of it this way Adam I was Eve bringing him food in the garden
he did the first sin which was sloth laziness
he was too lazy to get his own meal he told Eve that one gave him the meal and she brought him
The wrong fruit
Well, that reminds me of like, you know the lioness aren't the female
Lions like a lioness isn't that like the hunter of the food? Yeah, and they're lions
It's around in the sun preening and sometimes it's in bites and stuff, but
females catching the prey and things and you know
carrying children so she did females I think have a fierce protective over the young too and so
There's this like, you know power that we don't even understand that they have over protection of protection and strength
It's not a man's world. It's the devil's world
The world belongs to the devil
The whole world
It says that
Satan Lucifer is not even in hell is on this earth and this world is his role
You know the story of
Just don't tell you that psyche
Right. Well, it sounds like you know, I've heard about you know, God asked
Basically say until I kneel down or something like that and there's a similar story in the Koran where it's like I've lived
Because the Koran
Alar is obviously not God because he says
kill Jesus
disciples and you get you get a whole house in heaven
But the Muslim religion, it is an Abrahamic faith, you know, so it did grow out for me to say, you know, the sentence of Abraham, right?
It wasn't an Isaac and Ishmael or whole Isaac and the East out and I'm trying but don't listen to me, right?
It's like I'm telling the truth. Sure
The extreme Muslims wouldn't give no second chance of throwing me you off the roof
I understand that I understand gay people like a lot of them in some countries will put them against like a brick wall and you know
Here, you know knock it down up on top of them and stuff like that
I think Islam is the worst religion from Catholicism. It's the worst religion
They stone women in their country
They're getting great. Oh
Which is sad
You know, I don't think it's, well, I don't know, maybe you won't dislike me for saying that Islam is very, they blame women for everything, don't they?
You're in the second class students, they have to work, they have to walk 10 steps behind a man.
They have to wear hijabs, they're not allowed to go outside, they're not allowed to go and make doctor's appointments.
Have you ever seen the documentaries about Saudi love and beauty?
That's why I would never visit there.
You know, like African women and women from Philippines, what they'll do is,
they'll take women who are poor from them countries, they'll offer them a job in Saudi Arabia.
They'll take the passports off them, and then they'll use them as slaves.
Yeah, in a harem, like a sex slave, sex slave, and they'll do it to American women, they'll
traffic American women out there, take the passport away, right?
And then they're stuck in this like, you know, palace of this like, unfriendly kind of country
in this like, where they look away from like, you know, the royalty or the rich doing these
kind of crimes, right?
I wish the West would fight against the Middle East, to be honest, because I want it to stop.
I want women to have just as much right to go to the beach, that women want their jobs.
There's just as much right as a male does.
Well, I've seen like, in some countries they say something called the Burkini.
It's like a stupid diving outfit practically. Okay, we have gaudi up here
Not too bad. It's uh, it's me gaudi
Of course. Yeah, I just called I wasn't feeling too good man. I'm gonna have to call in sick
Yeah, I'm coming in sick. I'm sick. I'm sick of your shit. Oh my god. I'm sick of your shit, man. You got to knock this shit off. I'm sick of your shit.
Can someone, someone, someone go.
I'm fucking sick.
Africa's joke inside. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I love that. I was like if I had like five mods
He would definitely be one of the mods. I would keep if I had to like get them to five month
He's one of them. I think Jamie and Goddy
DJ I think in the West in England and America in
Europe we should ban the burger and
I'll tell you the reasons why
is because under a burger you can't see if a woman's getting abused physically
you can't see her face, you can't see if she's got bruises, burnt marks or anything
and I just, I just think it's a way of controlling
I don't, I don't like organised religions, even though I believe in the Bible and stuff
use the Bible to abuse and control people and manipulate people I
Do believe in the Bible?
But I don't believe it's supposed to be used as a tool as manipulation
Yeah, and that's what religion is basically like a lot of religion organized religion is used as a
Manipulation washing and programming of the society the culture and things right? Yeah
Do you think God's disciples, Jesus' disciples, were perfect people?
No, Peter kept making mistakes all the fucking time, didn't he?
Excuse me for anything.
Well, we know, like, you know, we're certainly Judas.
Judas did a lot of stuff.
And yeah, none of them, they were even...
Well, like, really, there's no perfect human.
have sinning. Right? It's like, yeah, if we say we don't sin, we're making a lie. And then the way it lies, right? But also, also because we're not like immortal in these bodies in our human bodies, that gives us the ability to be reborn, maybe, or just to like live in this experience in a temporary, temporary way.
Maybe corrupt it a little bit part of it is
Oh, you got even left already some people are driven by doubting him doubting Thomas right correct
I think people twist the Bible sometimes and they use the words and then they go and twist it
That's why I don't go to any church. I don't go to no church
I even tried seven-day Adventist church, even though I believe in soul sleep when we die
And I don't believe there's a help. I didn't appreciate the seven-day Adventist church
I don't believe people should be dressed in suits
and I don't think you should count your righteousness on the outside
if you know what I mean I think it counts inside
you can't see and you can't see the inside so it's very easy to disguise the outside it looked
pious and holy but it's like and it's I mean it's fine to like aspire to some kind of
Perfection. I mean I have an anxiety so when I have an anxiety right like I go outside for a cigarette more
So obviously I went into this church. I'm not a racist person
But when I went in there, we was the only white people in the church
And I understand what it's like for a black person to walk into a church for the white people.
It's very, it's very scary because, you know, you're the only people that are different.
Right.
We have like the I live very nearby the Jehovah's Witness
Church like it's cross three basically and
There's a lot of African-Americans and it's like it's really nice to see there's also like and they do are they are well-dressed and things like that
But they're also all races over there and you can see but they're also very a little bit culty a little bit like this like they're all
Dining outside then they go inside and close the door. It's kind of right. Um, I mean
I remember when I was a kid the joe's witness is always used to come around on christmas day
Right in the middle when you're eating your fucking christmas dinner and you're like
Interrupting your nice happy time, you know
Same with those preachers that come on the beach or go to pride
Marchers and they like oh, you're all going to hell when they don't know the people themselves
I talked to Dora love is an ignorant prick. I don't know if you know Dora love
He's like the head of one of the preachers
marches against the lgbd community or whatever and he goes he puts on his
titles of his video his horrible demon possess
Blah blah blah on his horrible titles. He's judging every single person he meets
and I went on his panel once to
Correct him about the Bible
And he was so rude to me and he was
Interrupting me. He was telling me to go to this verse and that verse when I already knew the verses in the Bible and
You know what he did he kicked me off. He won't let me have a voice
Let's take a quick look at my window. We have the gardeners outside.
Ignorant.
Oh, gosh, that.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know. I don't know if like, you know, I know you wouldn't form on my show
So I'm not very concerned. I won't do it. I promise you I'll swim
Yeah
She form mom somebody they probably deserve it
Yes, I did I did it so somebody who deserved it. She was talking shit on me and I lifted my top and shed my teeth
I will be honest, I went, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I said, Marty, it's right on the street.
You're a bitch.
Don't talk down to me like that.
It's a friend of mine.
I believe that she's a friend of mine.
She wouldn't do that to me.
Like I would I just like I went on and on who's the guy's name is a groupie Jimmy
I went on one day and I you know pulled down my pants and had the speedo on and
You know
I wouldn't do that. Yeah, just anybody
I'm all right
Come on. I don't
I've gone to school who I do it to
And the only time I've ever done it on white two bags was when this woman dropped a towel
And showed her boobs and I thought and it's it's become a funny story actually
And I thought fuck yeah, I'm gonna get my tits. I'm not gonna leave her. I got my tits out after she got her tits out
Well, you know, I didn't get a
It's freeze more popular now he's a
He's Adam some guy. I can't remember his name from
What's that bloody black head guys with the shades on
There's a who like you're talking about a streamer or
He knows that guy with the black curly hair that looks kind of looks like slush
Weirdo Yankevic
No
Traffic of his name is a talk
Yeah, that's it. He's a friend of Howard Sterns and he went on white two bucks
Well, I see Howard Stern was allowed to have people flashing. I mean, I mean, I kind of like, you know, I'm very inspired by him. People are always like, oh, you do think you're Howard Stern? I was like, I don't. I, uh, I...
Hey, you should subscribe to me, you know, Psyche. I'll put the link in the private chat. He's a fantastic guy.
Yeah.
You like him. He's alright.
Yeah
Be happy to subscribe to anybody you recommend. It's what's going on. Yeah, why are you park?
What's his name? I'm sorry
White to park. Okay, white to park and he's on YouTube
Okay, he's great. He's I see him. He's a he's very nice looking dark very dark skin. Okay, let me see
And he's
Okay, I'm doing right now, right? Okay. Well, yeah, oh, this is interesting. Someone was like, uh, let me see. So his name is White Tupac. Um, that's his channel name, Mike Tupac. Yeah, it's coming up and talking about it.
Like a bulldog or something
I have to look through YouTube, okay white people with the letter in the number the number two
Where they okay to yeah to
white
Yeah, I'm uh interested in checking him out. Okay. Oh
He's he's a dog on his thing. Oh, I think that's a YouTube drinking community if you like a nice drink
If you like drinking that's the best place to go. I
Did I didn't say hang out this guy named his name is L
C I think his name is LC and
He he's in Australia and he used to just drink and we just drink a lot of beers on a show and stuff like that
I'm a drinker. Can you believe I've drank almost all that bottle and I'm not that
pissed. I used to drink so much on my show. I used to get drunk every night. Every night.
Now I don't really drink that much. This is terrible for me. I used to drink almost
two of these.
Well this person see it. That's why I guess why guys I tell you block people
I tell you to block is that my call person now saying he's trying to do a doc seven people or whatever I mean guys
I've already been dox, but I don't want anybody but he's trying to scare people. It's like you know
He's not gonna do anything
but
Unfortunately, we have like these monsters here that we're gonna threaten us. Don't don't don't like give into fear of these
These people just want to scare people, right?
So, um, you know peps are saying your peps 2.0. I don't know why they're saying that
Seems very different peps. I don't even know what means
And then Zaya is that peps it and peps is actually really cool. I hung out with her before
Bex yep
Um, um, but I think maybe I'm kind of like I'm kind of like mom. I either like me or you don't like me
Everybody likes me. Well, some people like me
I certainly do. I think uh, I give a great personality. You're super interesting. I was telling somebody I was like
Yeah, she um
Telling somebody that I knew somebody that had an experience but the days a little in the astral realm and
had you know
Being actually seeing kind of these astral beings kind of interesting. She's not cool to the terrible person
Well, you know what she was kind to me
I don't know. I mean I was on her show three diamond ones and she was kind to me but
Riz come on. Are you being that as everyone being cool? I hope everyone's been cool
I'm just now calling. I'm drinking the night time. I'm a coffee hauler. I've been drinking a lot of coffee.
The only problem is I drink every night. I've got an husband, you know.
He takes care of the night time for me.
I still get up in the morning and cook the dinners and do my sheet.
You know you somebody was asking about you this I think somebody was saying that they had
Could not access your Facebook page, and I tried to explain to them
I don't know if you know I'm talking about or if that was like oh, yeah, I blocked him. I blocked him. I got you
Well, yeah, I won't go into it
Me about ten times. I won't say the name, but he rang me about ten times. Okay, then I declined
I just declined you rang again
Decline ring again decline ring again decline
Does he not realize that I press decline? I'm busy
Don't bother me
Yeah, I tried to explain as I keep that is
That kind of thing it's too much for me
I have to do with my own mental health. I can't be dealing with somebody else's
And I would say to be very careful about giving away any kind of like number or contact to anybody
No, because there are people that will just give out your number and stuff like that
Just be just be very careful about sharing personal information
Yeah, I know I've accidentally docked myself a couple of times
I didn't realize when I'm sharing my Amazon page
It shows your address at the top
Yeah
I don't know and I've talked to myself a couple of times and I've had people try and send me pieces and stuff like that
But luckily I've got that dog behind me. Oh, sorry somebody's talked to my address in the chat
Oh, they are oh come on. Oh my gosh
That's not appropriate
Is it my child see it? I'll see but they do that. I'm sorry, you know, um
Yeah, any doxing mods, you know hit immediately, right? No, we're gonna hide all these people. Oh my gosh
I'm so sorry. Who is that person? I mean
Why are you doxing me, you know that person or no, oh my god
He's getting angry get angry for some reason. I don't know what I've done wrong
Just time
Because anybody that will do that, they're not going to like, you know, improve.
Like I was saying, people were saying, I'm going to send some people to Psyche's house and then...
He has helped me fix my computer a couple of times.
Because obviously I'm a bit computer illiterate and he's helped me fix my computer.
Um, Riz, what do you talk about the pizza? So is this Riz? Are you are you doxing Riz?
Oh Riz is mad because I admire him. Who is this Riz person? I can I know Riz, but that's not him.
No, my dog went crazy. Me dog behind me went crazy
With the door knocking all the time because I got one of those knockers on the door. I was tap-tap-tap
She had an O
I opened the door and I couldn't stop her, she barged past me, chased the fucking delivery man
all the way down to the fucking gate.
I didn't order that, I'm sorry about my dog, but I didn't order that.
I
Send you a paid-for pizza. I've never gotten that one. I only got the manure sense that was paid for
Before but I've never had paid takeaways now
Well, I have actually I've had a couple people send me that some nice dinners and stuff like that
You're not mod or not mad. Okay, but you're talking about why are you thinking?
Nothing drives me no, so it drives the dog nose
Yeah, I ended up in the door door low key and
The dog dashes out
And chases the delivery man down the fucking pathway
Well, if you don't answer the door like looky, I think you should just tell the delivery person is not involved in like the harassment
I mean they just start deliver doing their job, right?
So it's better just to say, you know, I didn't order it and they send them on their way
So they're not just knocking for half an hour, right? I mean, it's like or just put a sign on the door, right?
I mean, it's like yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, you don't want to open it like if you have a dog running out. No, but my cats they if they hear a knock on the door
They will
Just open the door a little bit and she just barged away past me
Yeah
Well, you got a little good little guard guard for you, you know
My cats I wish I had a guard cat, you know, like but the cats are a little bit
Children I've seen have you ever seen that video that went viral
the one where
This dog comes and attacks a little kid on the driveway
Oh, no comes dashing out and fucking attacks dog. Oh
I
Seen like an inside edition they had like
They're testing, like this lady's dog, they're testing to see what would happen if somebody
came in the house, and this lady's dog was not very brave, but some of them were, I guess,
a real many times a ladder, rung by rung.
You know, I love watching them reels of dogs where they're so kind.
You see them running to protect little babies and children and all that.
I fucking love it.
I saw a bear.
A bear was trying to break into the house and the dog chased away the bear.
That was just recently.
That was amazing.
And the dog chased the bear all the way out of the yard and stuff.
I like to see the love animals have got, and I like hearing about stories about where there was, did you hear about that story about a kid that went into a gorilla's pen?
Is that that one?
She guarded the gorilla.
What was that gorilla's name?
They killed the gorilla though, didn't they?
It was named something.
No.
I'm not only about that one.
I've seen a real way.
This baby was in this toddler and this month this gorilla picked you up and passed it to the mother
Oh, I've seen that one. Yeah
Well, it's like there's somewhere that was a one where the kid wins the gorilla cage
The really didn't do anything, but they still shot the gorilla and stuff and it's like
Well, let's say put days so today is Wednesday, right?
Have you ever heard about this story about a pride of lions in Africa, where there was
these bandits trying to capture this lass and they tried to kidnap a rite and take her
Where the lion's all
The lion's heard her crying
They came and attacked the people that kidnapped her
And they kept they kept an eye on the girl till she got rescued. Have you ever heard of that story?
What's beautiful, I remember it like a little bit of Daniel and lion's den where he was thrown to be eaten by the lions and then
He comes out unscathed because he was so good with cats, you know, and I kind of feel like I would be like that too
I feel like I could like charm the lion or actually
Wasn't the story that he actually was raised around the lion and then they so they remembered him or something
I don't remember exactly, but yeah
Yeah
I think God tries his best to help us, you know, so like I think he tries his best to help us all out
But sometimes he can't always get everybody
God, yeah, I think sometimes everything even some things are out of his power
We can't get to rescue people
Like if there's no animals there by the side
If there's nothing there
He can't stop the toddler from drowning in a pond or something like that and
That's why it's a sad story
because
I mean God can't come down on the earth because they would destroy us all
Right, but he can work through the different creatures or what's around and things like that
There's nothing is there's nothing around there's nothing he can do about it
Yeah, there's difficult lessons, you know, it's like a
In Buddhism they talk a lot about you know
like the
You know
being able to like
You know karma and stuff like that so sometimes bad things happen so that they can be reborn in a better life or something like that
And it's planned out. I don't know it's interesting to think about so I believe that like life is eternal for everybody
Right. I mean it's like where everybody's this it has a piece of eternity inside of them
The energy cannot be created or destroyed. It can only change form. So if everything is just constantly
recycling, you know over over time
You did you ever believe like when it rains it's called crying. Oh
It's a beautiful thought, you know, or uh, you know
Angel gets his wings when there's a or what or freckles are like angel kisses kind of too, right?
I don't know if it got crying. I don't know. It's a
You know that song where it says snowflake little snowflake. I find that very sweet on its song, you know
It's like why?
It's I think
Snowflake
Yeah, and it's like a snowflake. Have you ever heard that every snowflake is a different snowflake?
correct
Like snowflakes are people falling from the sky
You know when it goes, that's why I find that song creepy when it goes snowflake, snowflake, little snowflake, falling, falling, falling, falling, falling, falling.
It's kind of hard made out of mostly watery, you know, and so, you know, snowflake is mostly frozen water, right?
It's like human beings falling down to earth, you know.
Mm-hmm like the angels fell too like the spirit falls to the earth and then it like rises up
And then it's just it's like the rain right it like falls and then it like it's evaporated up into like back into this thing
And it rains again to a cloud and then back into the and it's all the same water from the beginning of time
It's all been the same water, right?
It's all sorry
Rory's got story
Yeah, three lions protect 12-year-old girl from kidnappers in Ethiopia till the police arrived amazing story, right?
Reckles our angel kisses gingers are
Right to park check see if it's the original
Yeah, subscribe to your channel
The channel a lot of you post this channel in the chat
I think it probably is a lot of subscribers. If it's a real white two
Yeah, it is. It is. Okay. Looking forward. Yeah.
Come on. Right. Two Park. Come on. Yeah. I'm just saying how great you are.
I don't know.
Just so what he's protected. I have a game a mod a black mark. Yeah
I mean, but there there's so many things that are like metaphors that are like just beautiful these beautiful metaphors
And it's even our life is a symbolic something
I think our life is in everything is symbolic in the world, right?
Especially if you look out for every kind of animalism there's a meaning to and if you see it some kind of animal
There's gonna be something that because we're all the animals. I believe I believe that Adam was the king of the animals
And the tall one, they said he slept with all the animals.
I'm not quite sure about that,
but that'd be interesting to see.
He's up with every beast of the field,
but some of them were like insects and fire, I don't know.
Interesting.
Butterflies, what do you think of butterflies?
You think they're, Nicole Kidman once said,
she doesn't find anything more terrifying than a butterfly.
She just found them very creepy.
What do you think?
Do I want to paint the design on the wings?
Oh, who designs the wings, right?
You'll paint who designs the wings?
Yeah, you know, I've got different patterns on them.
Yeah
Greek mythology they have like the West wind is like named Zephyrus and there's like different names for the winds and they're actually like
you know put into these kind of beings that
represent the winds because I
Yeah, I'm gonna post the link if anyone wants to come up and say hi come on up guys like we're just having a nice
So hot here today. It is like probably about 90 degrees outside here today. Hey
Yeah
And I'm just sitting with my cat and we're all,
I got the dryer going so I was putting some heat
in the room too and I had the floor.
You're in the background, you got a picture
with a woman in a school.
Yeah, I'll show you.
Oh yeah, there we go.
I think it's kind of like Mary Magdalene a little bit,
but I can make all kinds of, it's basically a poster.
You know, it's a green screen,
so I can put any kind of picture,
I can change it like that, see.
Wow, cool.
Yeah, I got a stream yard. They have that setting where I can change things around. I do like that
That look, you know, I you got the old painting looks
I generated that through AI that this one, you know, and it's like came out pretty good
Some people say I look like Mona Lisa
The Mona Lisa
Yeah, the pain
Yeah, I've just got those two drives, you know, there's two drives
Do you like this picture? Do you know who this is right here?
Yeah, you know not the old eyes
What do you call it? Arnglouce Harkson. Yeah
I think that's it. This is like a depiction of Hecate, I think
Part of her she's like the Greek goddess of magic and witchcraft
What's this one right here? Oh, yeah, there's there's me with Lilith
Yeah, you what do you think of Lilith?
Don't know
Have you heard of her?
You've heard of Lilith, right?
I've heard of her she's in
Tudan mythology
Well, she's in the actually there's something in the Bible where it's like talked about the
But it means
There is a separate part in Genesis
Two and Genesis three. It says in Genesis two he made them
Yes, you know a man later. He creates a woman
But at first they're equal right I'm sorry to mean or interrupt, but yeah, yeah
Yeah, I mean so then they think the
Describes would look into that and so in the Talmud, which is like the oral tradition
They would it elaborate on every like little name and stuff like that and they come up with other stories about it
And so then they have the story of Lilith. It's something called the alphabet of Ben Sirah
Which is maybe like a little bit of a pseudo
100% because linear
I wanted to name my first child after Lilith and I am not miscaraging.
If Lilith can cause miscarriages and stuff.
I've heard that.
Yeah.
I'm not a nice person.
I think that people should be careful about naming children after Goddesses or things
like that because sometimes I think the Goddess can take them as a sacrifice or sometimes
I don't know it's gonna be quite a fake quite a name to live up to you, right?
It's so funny when you give me names are very important, right? So the weird thing, right?
I was told that my son my first child
Even though I never got to see what sex it was because I miscarried it while we try and sign
My son warned me when he was a little toddler
And he says what's those marks on you told me mom I said oh it's stretch marks
From where he was kicking. I said it wasn't me mom. It was my brother max
So he told me that the child was a boy
It's like a twit was in his twin or that was his brother or who?
It was his older brother
I showed you these, did I show you like some marks on my arm?
I woke up one morning with like a burn,
like a strange burn on my arm.
And then of course in this community,
everyone's very skeptical and they were like,
oh, you got drunk and you like, you know,
burned yourself or I did it to myself.
I, on my life, I woke up,
I remember like I was completely sober
before I fell asleep.
And then I woke up with this burn and I showed you the burn.
It's still here months later.
Look, and it's like a, it's really strange.
You see them?
I mark right there.
There's three, there's three scratches.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And then it's like, you know, I get me,
people are just so skeptical, but it's like,
I do believe like that something happened in my dream
with either a succubus, because I am like a,
I don't know if you've seen my tattoo, but.
What's this? Is that a female demon? Yes. I thought you were gay though. I
am but I
Don't know if that's I do believe in like the onima and also I got that when I was 18
Oh, that was my first tattoo. I'm sure you're not bisexual. Do you get a little tinge from a woman before yeah
I did date a woman. I would make you bisexual then it would make you born
Right, but my main attraction is I think maybe like I'd like you know
I think Alexander said Alexander said I was like 90% masculine 10% feminine. I think I'm maybe like, you know
Little bit more in the middle. I'm feeling pretty balanced
I think I'm pretty balanced with my feminine side
But I do believe that we have the onima which is the inner feminine and that's like the spirit and you can call it different
You call it
What do you fancy the most? Do you fancy males or females?
I have a type and I like kind of like the bad
you know the bad boy tattoo, the shaped head, I like the Latino
like a lot, I kind of like they're kind of dangerous to date
and so I kind of like don't let myself date too much because I've gotten into
a little bit of trouble dating some of the bad boys but
I'm attracted to them, but then again, I've always been around beautiful women, like I've just always had things around them, my mother's beautiful, my sister's beautiful, like, and then I've always had beautiful friends, you know, and so, I think I, I just love, I love beauty, you know, I do love beauty, but I think that beauty, I think love beauty, and I just love beauty.
He went through a phase when he was younger he didn't he didn't know he didn't know whether he was a good boy
He had a mother
And he had a father, but his father wore a pony tail
so I
Think he couldn't tell whether he was male or female
Time is asking about my Russian friend. I'm gonna show you a picture of my rush. I have a Russian friend
She just got out of prison like a little bit ago. She just got her high school diploma
She's really I said I went through some kind of like, you know
I learned a lot about mind control from the she grew up in Russia of course, right?
And she's pretty you know, she was pretty
Pretty good at the mind control stuff, but I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble. Hold on. I just want to show you something
Let's see, I want to show you this picture, but here she is, this is what she's doing, she does a little bit of AI too.
Well, here's what she looks like here with my friend, my Russian friend.
Here, and then here she is as a firefighter, hold on.
Well, she loves cats too, so she has the cat doing it.
That's Rudy, but she did Rudy as AI, and then she's like my future life, and so she was on a firefighter program.
There she is right there.
in her little AI firefighter outfit.
And I think she looks really tall here.
She's not that tall, I don't think,
but she really is this beautiful though.
I mean, she's pretty gorgeous, huh?
I'm in big trouble actually, but I just saw a text message
and I'm in big trouble with somebody.
Okay, Jamie, I'm in trouble.
You know why?
Okay, I don't know if we're gonna get an interview.
I did show my friends some of the clips of like, you know, I've been clipped on a trip kick several times
I don't know if she's she is very pretty. Yeah, I've been
I was trying to look for
Young Google I was trying to look for big women art and this seemed to removed a lot of artist paintings off the internet
You remember in the old days when you used to go through Greek mythology books
Yes, you see a lot of big women
I basically my tattoo is based on Ann and Nicole Smith, I don't know if you've heard of her but
I tried googling it because I wanted to use one from my avatar and I couldn't find one
It's like they've put all the when you look for a big woman. They just put like a
Size 14 to 16. They don't put like really big women on there
Right, but you know if you look at those statues like here
I mean, I can't really like some of them are nude and stuff like that
But like this one is not too bad here. Here's like an old statue of Venus
Yeah, you know she's a little bit more on the thick side a little bit a little thicker
And
But that's and that's the goddess of beauty and there's also let me see
I can find I put the love she was goddess and it's like they're all so skinny
Why is it to call the do you remember Ruben? I think it was Ruben
Ruben s right?
Yeah
Why is it to pull that off the internet?
Strange here's a like a Ruben s figure. Well, this one's a little bit
That one's a little that one's really big. Hold on. Let me find
Make women's star
Well, have you seen the original Venus was trying to say normal women are fat
They are
This one kind of looks like you a little bit
Little bit different hair to me. She's normal though. She's like childbearing woman
Yeah, I think well, yeah, I love the full up. She was
Yeah, the bigger big women are
I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I think, you know, I
But you know they used to I mean that it means like you know to be like have like a large hips was like
You know child bearing means you can be a healthy give healthy delivery. There's a beautiful one here
Pretty
Yeah
That is a Rubin S. Yeah, I want women to feel confident when they're vodka
Right, I mean, it's like I think that we're like a little bit, you know, I'm very women have took
before women's had three kids
That's 27 months of pain and
Sacrifice a woman should not be it may need to feel bad
Thought about a body afterwards my mom had five
Mom had five kids, you know five she gave birth to five and
Wow, I always appreciate like women and my mother or you know anybody that you know all mothers like you know have
Sacrifices you know women are women like to have a tight belly and suffer sometimes and it's like that to have a baby
You're belly gets stretched out like this or vagina has a watermelon coming out of it and all those kind of stuff
So it is a sacrifice, but they love it if you hate it so much. I'm certified scary guy
Why are you here? Like if like why are you putting yourself?
Like can someone just hide that first? I don't understand my people
want to be places where they hate. I don't like that. Some of these people are just nuts.
Some refer to Lilith as a succubus in Dreams. Yes, Lilith is known as the queen of the succubus,
you know, and so I do, I can show you that this is like the Lilith's picture again. This is my third,
I'm a, there's an astrological Lilith, which is Lilith in Scorpio, but I do picture her similar to
You know
She's tall and tall and taller than me. I'm six foot three so she must be a giant
Yeah, it's certified scare is that that person's still there. I'm not gonna be
Thank you, Jamie is thank you, Jamie
Hey, gang. Hey, everybody. Hey,
Hey, gang. Hey, gang. Hey, gang. Hey,
Marilyn Monroe, I have a Jane Man still May West was very Buxom. Yeah. Oh my gosh
And this is like the trolls are out today. Hey summer. Oh, is it summer there? No, it was Samantha. I hate Samantha. What's up? Okay?
Thank you, Jamie. Thank you. Oh, I got the person I got the person. Thank you so much, Jamie. I
Yeah, I just got these people saying HIV and stuff in the chat like
She horrible. Oh
Yeah, do you want I can show you I don't know if everyone saw this clip
I do want to play a little bit of this but this is like the terror reading I did for this woman
It's called the most chaotic terror reading in the world or something. Oh, actually
I think she may have overdosed that or maybe she was
Don't worry about it. She's not coming back
I don't really judge okay, do you think marry monroe?
I heard what do you think she was saying for the president she's saying for JFK or something right and
What do you think Gordie? JFK killed her they were having rough sex
Hello is it freezing for everybody else it's freezing for me
It's called climate change. I don't read for people that are haters Mike sorry
You heard of it? Hogsmeade?
Is that in English? Yeah, it's in English.
You heard of it? Have you, Natalie, Hogsmeade?
Hogsmeade. We've been to Hogsmeade.
Have you heard of that, Natalie? Hogsmeade?
No. She froze. Well, I haven't, but I've been
Hogsmeade. I've never been there, no.
Yeah, it's a cool place. They also have a place called olivanders. They've been to olivanders
Olivanders, olivanders
Olive, olivanders, like never heard of me. Olivanders
Oh, it's great. I've been to
My brother-in-law was from Manchester, so I got to stay in Manchester for a little while
And I went to Canal Street in Manchester. Oh
Canal Street's nice. Yeah, it's real nice
Look at the smoke. I love the smoke. Have you ever been to Lloyds of London?
What about Lloyds Lloyds Lloyds of London?
I've never been there. Have you been to the Tavistock Institute?
No never
Tavistock is where they came up in Scotland. It's Tavistock England and that's where they
Invented the Beatles and most most music right came out of the Tavistock. It's a
Think tank where they basically do the programming of the music for the masses and things like that to program the culture
Yeah
Myself I hate the fucking Beatles. I hate the Beatles. I don't like them very much either. I think they're kind of like they're overrated
There's God is trolling right now. You're trolling up. What's going on? You know who's better than the Beatles was the the monkeys
Hey, hey, where the monkeys
Who said I'm trolling no, no someone in the chat said oh god, um, they said
He said he knows I'm God trolling right now
It's yikes, I guess they're from England and the guy's a different HIV awakened hero is
Listen, who cares what they say, dude, we know it's not true
Don't even read the name out. I know but I want to hear that there's like people the sick that would do that
That would be under that name. Okay. My phone is ringing. Okay. Yeah, there's people that is sick
One of you wants for dinner it's bloody 16 bus 11 at night why?
What's make me a little...
Dinner's over.
We're running.
We're a little mushy peas.
Is that a real Gotti?
The fake Gotti, it's the fake Gotti.
I don't think that's a real Gotti.
I fucking fooled you all, it's the fake Gotti.
Gotti, come on.
I fucking fooled you all now I will destroy you what are you gonna do what are you gonna
destroy I'm gonna destroy you with my dick you ready oh yeah about it about
I'm going to bow down to you.
You're going to bow now.
You're going to bow.
You're going to beg for it.
Yeah, right.
I'm going to hold my head up high.
Let me hear you beg.
Let me hear you beg, bud.
Be a good bud and beg for it.
Let me hear you.
Thank you.
Kiss my butt.
Kiss like a dog.
Park like a dog.
Kiss my also.
Park like a kiss my also like a taste the biscuit
Oi
Let me kiss my also like
Let me hear you guys
Let me hear you guys kiss
Natalie
She always comes on the line
Every time I see little Natalie
She always trips so on a vine.
I just made that up, huh? Is that great?
Yes, Gotti, lovely.
I'm a bloody wizard.
Why?
Oh, there's Lilith.
Lilith, what's up, bitch?
Oh, she's screaming. That's not good.
Oh my gosh, she needs some dental work.
Oh, that's good. Did you hear that?
She needs some dental work.
You have good teeth.
No, you know what? You've got good teeth
for an English woman.
I've got this in teeth, to be honest.
I'm planning on getting some dental implants soon.
Yeah, but compared to most Brits,
I mean, that's like a complete set.
Now I've got missing one
Now I've never seen him before. Oh my god, you're going out with Lisa. Yeah, Lisa, you know Lisa. She's a good bird
Isn't he gonna
They're a couple of people yeah supposedly they're going out. Yeah, I wish them all the best
It doesn't matter what you look like, you know
Why I'm gonna say golly is your penis will shrivel up one day my vagina will go dry as a desert
We will not be able to vote but we could still don't worry. They got medication for that
We'll still be able to cuddle we'll hose you down you'll be fine
It's like you left us alone, that's not good
Wonder what it's like when you don't when you men are pausing and it's like you're fucking on the dry desert
I'm perimenopause or something. Oh, oh, pretty. Oh, okay. I
Be getting
I don't mean to be TMI, but I'm getting heavier periods
You're flowing extra that means it's yeah, it's running its course
Actually, I'm not being gross. I'm letting women know what the end stages are like. So
If anybody doesn't want TMI go and watch Nickelodeon or something
Because this is a 21 plus stream if you don't like fucking crooners
Go watch go watch Peppa Pig
You know what? You know what? I would suggest anyone stop giving your mobile phones to your
babies because you know Peppa Pig, you can put Peppa Pig on but there's an evil Peppa
Pig in there where she goes bludgeoning people with baseball bats.
Yeah, I like it. I like it. I
Put I put pepper pig home from my door when she was younger
And suddenly
It was alright. I could have a big blah blah blah blah
That's only I had this
pepper pig everything in blinding
I'm talking about measuring people with a baseball bat or something, and I'm like,
I've got to get out.
You could have never seen me go for that phone so fast.
I'm like, what the hell?
That's supposed to be a better thing.
Oh, I blimey, that's a pepper pig story it is.
Because you know when you put pepper pig on it rotates around and around and around.
And if there's that bad pepper pig it gets mixed in with the rest.
I'm going to make you rotate around and around and around.
I love that you like me to go around and around around around
You want to spend like a washing machine? Oh, yeah, spin me around baby around around
Like a record player yeah twist me like a pretzel baby
Treat my legs like they're plasticine, you know that did you ever see what I look like?
No, let me show you. This was taken yesterday
There's gonna be a yes
You're gonna put a head is I have the beholder, you know
Yeah
We don't judge
or any day now
or your friend
Why are you men so slow?
Let me machine
You know what girls
Is that you oh
That's kind of
You like that, huh? I knew I don't freak
Don't bite down
I smell minty fresh
Talk go stop
You ever see a ghost?
In real life? Never.
I thought my grandpa was at the bottom of the stairs once when I was a kid.
I imagined him at the bottom of the stairs, but it wasn't him.
Obviously.
Oh, you thought it was your grandfather?
Yeah, because when he died, the last memory I had was him giving me a whooping, a good eyeing.
That's not a good last memory. As far as last memories go, that's horrible.
Yeah, I was about, and then I got blamed for killing him.
Ah jeez, that's even worse.
a devil child that never left you you're traumatized by that event yeah but now
I went I even was traumatized so bad like I got weed you bored to try and talk
to him to tell him I'm sorry Natalie Natalie you got to forgive yourself you
just got to let it go and just forgive yourself that's it
I don't know if it was him or not, but he said, I'm okay, I'm with you, none of them.
I'm God, it was him. He said, you're okay, you're okay.
I absolve you of any wrongdoing.
He had PTSD, you see, he wasn't a bad man, he would just have PTSD and I was running around screaming.
And he couldn't take the screams because it brought on his PTSD because obviously if all in the world war two
He was raised to bring up children give a whopping you gotta whip the child
What do they say spare the child beat the shit out of the kid spare the rod
Gonna beat your kid sometimes let them know who's boss
Come here, you brat
You know what happens if you don't beat your kids
Well, they turn to this
There's that that's a ghost
You don't want your kids to turn into a ghost
It looks like it still lives with mom
There you go
Is it still living ways mom yeah, he's a mommy boy
He crashes out every night
Go to your room. I'm finna crash out, mom. I'm finna crash out. I'm gonna run it back.
You heard?
If my son wasn't that bad, I'd kick him out, send him to a grandma's. She'll soon whip
him in shape.
Thanks, Smash. Thanks, pal. I appreciate it, pal. You know, any compliment from Smash goes
a long way.
So what's going on tonight? What are you doing?
Don't know I need to go pee in a minute. Well go pee. I'll be waiting here
When you get back, so I don't want you to piss you don't piss your bloomers
Now I'm not gonna piss myself. I'm not
Wash your hands
Can you hear me?
Did she go?
Did she go? I tricked her. I'm gonna leave when she comes back. There's not gonna be anybody here.
Ready? One,
two,
Hi, sorry about that.
And somebody come to the door looking for a lawn mower.
Can you believe it?
Natty?
Uh-oh.
Guys, I'll be back in a little bit, okay?
Thank you, Natty, for being on the show.
Love you guys.
I'll be back.
I've been missing in my sleep